人人影视
YYeTs.com
原创翻译  双语字幕
■
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新
请登陆www.YYeTs.com
翻译：Iz    奈奈良
校对：Iz          总监   IZ
时间轴：今        后期：吉吉
《开心汉堡店》
第三季第二十集
吉恩  桌子下面的口香糖
Gene, you almost done
你刮完了没
scraping the gum off the bottom of the counter?
快了  我的口香糖脑袋也快完成了
Yeah! And I'm almost done with Gumhead.
你好呀  口香糖脑袋
Here you go, Gumhead.
再来点口香糖
More gum!
吉恩  别闹了
Gene, knock it off.
我知道你以为自己是在帮忙
I know you think you're helping,
-但你并没有  -我没觉得我在帮忙
- but you're not. - I don't think I'm helping.
好了  来了啊
All right, step right up.
猜猜奶精在哪个杯子下面  蒂娜
Which cup is the creamer under, Tina?
把视线集中在奶精上  小美女
Keep your eye on the creamer, little lady.
-去哪儿了  去哪儿了  -露易丝
- Where's it going? Where's it going? - Louise.
咋了  老爸
Yeah, Dad?
-你知道奶精在哪儿吗  -不知道
- Do you know where the cream is? - No.
那就别管闲事
All right, then stay out of it.
在这儿吗  是这个吗  还是那个
Is it here? Is it this one? Is it that one?
-这个  -错了
- This one? - Wrong!
-现在你得把它喝了  -好吧
- Now you have to drink it. - Ugh. Okay.
蒂娜  露易丝  够了  去干活儿
Tina, Louise, enough, and get back to work.
这周是舰队周  对我们来说很重要
This is a big weekend for us. It's Fleet Week!
美国海军陆战队和美国海岸警卫队的传统  指最近被部署在海外的现役军舰  在主要城市停靠一个星期
耶  脚丫周
Yay! Feet Week!
不对  是舰队周
No. Fleet Week.
-怎么会有脚丫周这种东西  -谁知道
- Why would there be a Feet Week? - I don't know.
还有植树节这种东西呢  要它来干嘛
There's Arbor Day. Who needs that?
从此刻起  随时都会有士兵
Any minute now, sailors will be
从那扇门涌进来  点汉堡和啤酒
pouring through that door, wanting burgers and beer.
大部分是啤酒  但道理一样
Mostly beer, but still.
打扰了  先生
Excuse me, sir,
我要检查你的桌下有没有口香糖
but I need to inspect your table for gum.
走开  吉恩
Gene, get out of there.
不  口香糖脑袋还没嘴呢
No! Gumhead needs lips!
-把口香糖脑袋给我  -不要
- Give me the Gumhead. - Mm, no!
给我
Give me your Gumhead!
抱歉了  先生  吉恩
I'm sorry, sir. Gene!
把我的孩子还我
Give me back my son!
我要给他吹气赋予他生命
I just need to breathe life into him!
好了  蒂娜  新一轮来了  来了哦
All right, Tina, new game, new game.
视线集中在奶精上
Keep your eye on the cream.
别眨眼
Try not to blink.
吉恩  别打你妈  琳达  别踢他
Gene, don't hit your mother. Linda, don't kick him!
没猜着  又错了  喝  喝
You missed it! Wrong! Drink it! Drink it!
-露易丝  -麻烦埋单
- Louise? - Uh, check, please?
吉恩
Gene?
我靠  切到手了
Damn it! I cut my hand!
谁去撒泡尿在上面
Oh, somebody pee on it!
我刚尿过  真是场灾难
I just went pee! This is a disaster!
没事了  我没事
Oh. Never mind. It's okay.
我没流血  是误报
I'm not bleeding. False alarm.
你吓我一跳
Phew! You had me worried there.
你一流血就会头晕
You get so woozy when you bleed.
记得他用牙线剔牙那次不
Remember that time he flossed?
他直接栽马桶里了
He passed out right into the toilet.
-等等  -所以我都从来不用牙线
Oh, whoa, whoa. Wait. That's why I never floss.
流血其实就是你的牙齿在对你说
Blood is your teeth's way of saying,
"少管闲事"
"Mind your own business!"
-我只在生日那天用牙线  -各位
- I only floss on my birthday... - Guys.
这样我就能回顾我这一年都吃了什么
...so I can look back on the year and remember what I ate.
而且他还不能凝血  会有生命危险
Plus, he can't clot to save his life.
他的血会一直流  特别恶心
He bleeds forever. It's gross.
我真的  我真的在流血
I'm act... I'm actually bleeding here.
鲍鲍
Bobby?
你还好吧
You... okay?
我没事
I'm fine.
只是一点点血
It's just a little bluh...
我躺地上干嘛
What am I doing down here?
-你昏过去了  老爸  -不可能
- You passed out, Dad. - No, I didn't.
你确实昏了
Pretty sure you did.
也许你只是打了个小盹
Maybe you took a little catnap.
我没昏  蒂娜
I didn't pass out, Tina.
我摇摇欲坠的小鲍勃
Aw, my little Wobbly Bobbly.
"Wobbly Bobbly"也是一款名叫《糖果危机》的智力游戏
我去
Hmm. Oh, crap. All right.
我们得赶紧准备迎接午餐高峰
We got to finish prepping for the lunch rush.
-不行  -我没事  琳
- Uh-uh. - No, I'll be fine, Lin.
这可不好说  你切到指裆了
I don't know. You got cut right in the old finger crotch.
天  我们的家丑要泄漏了
Oh, no! Not the family finger crotch jewels!
各位  我说了我没事  这都没
Guys, I said it's fine. It's not even...
不  我的天
No. Oh, God.
好了  好了  我们走
Okay, okay, let's go.
你会一直流血的
You're not gonna stop bleeding.
好吧  我可能需要缝两针
Okay, I-I might need a couple stitches.
琳达  你留下来准备午餐高峰
Linda, you have to stay for the lunch rush.
我自己开车去
I'll drive myself.
我一个人没问...
It's not gonna be a prob...
你不能开车
Oh! Oh, you're not driving.
来  钥匙给我
Come on, give me the keys.
我们中午关门就行了
We'll just have to close for lunch.
要不了几个小时就能回来
We'll be back in a few hours.
我们可以照看餐馆啊
We could run the restaurant.
-不行  不行  -是啊  我们可以
- No, no. - Yeah, we can do it.
我们就跟人说老爸在洗澡
We'll just tell people that Dad's in the shower
老妈在上大号
and Mom's on the toilet.
为什么我要上大号
Why do I have to be on the toilet?
好吧  你们俩都在上大号
Fine, you can both be on the toilet.
然后老爸出去买烟就再也没回来
And Dad went out for a pack of smokes and never came back.
不不不  我们暂时休业
No, no, no. We're closing the restaurant
然后去医院
and we're going to the hospital, all right?
孩子们  上楼去
Kids, upstairs.
蒂娜  你当临时保姆
Tina, you're babysitting.
临时保姆倒计时开始
Countdown to babysitting.
让我们翘首以盼
Excitement begins now.
100  99  98
100, 99, 98...
四  三
Four, three,
二  一
two, one.
谁想玩好玩的呀
Who's ready for some fun?
你们说啥
I can't hear you.
我不排斥好玩的
I'd be open to fun.
来看看都有什么
Let's see here.
我们可以玩"鱼雷"  "拯救山姆"
We can play Torpedo, Surgery Sam,
还是你想发泄发泄
or if we need to blow off some steam,
那我们可以给老爸写一张早日康复卡片
we can make a get-well card for Dad.
缝针愉快  老爸  谁让你自作自受
"Happy stitches, Dad. You deserve it."
这个怎么样  能别那么嗦吗
Or how about, "Stitch, please!"
一词多义  "stitch"有缝针和让人闭嘴的意思
我才不想写什么卡片
Ugh, I don't want to make cards.
我想赚钱
I want to make money!
我提议我们去楼下开业挣钱吧
I say we go down there, and we open up for business.
好耶
Yeah.
可老爸老妈一小时后就回来了
But Mom and Dad will be home in an hour.
我们可以玩假装开餐馆的游戏嘛
Maybe we could play pretend restaurant?
我在装餐巾纸盒
I'm restocking the napkin dispenser.
吉恩  你去扫地
Gene, you go clean the floors.
既然是假装的  那我
If we're pretending, I'm...
我要做意大利白干酪
I'll make fresh mozzarella.
假餐馆赚不了钱  蒂娜
We're not making money in this fake restaurant, Tina!
时机未到而已  我们现在是做口头宣传
Not yet, but we're building good pretend word of mouth.
天  这会是我生命中最漫长的一小时
Oh! This is gonna be the longest hour of my life.
等你生过孩子再来说这话  姑娘
Wait till childbirth, girlfriend.
速战速决  两针五分钟搞定
In and out, two stitches, five minutes. Here we go.
我们来啦
We're doing it.
好吧  老妈  坏消息是
Okay, Mom. The bad news is,
老爸老妈一时还回不来
Mom and Dad are gonna take longer than they expected.
好消息是  我们有更多的游戏时间了
The good news is, now we have more time for activities.
可以玩更多的假装游戏
Like more pretending.
要不要假装我们有只狗然后喂他吃药啊
Should we pretend we have a dog and give it medicine?
我帮你想到了一个游戏
I've got an activity for you.
名字叫做
It's called...
开餐馆
...opening the restaurant.
孩子们要接管餐馆了
The kids are running Bob's Burgers, and this time
这次可是来真的
it's personal!
我要真的把它开到地下去
I'm gonna personally run it into the ground!
等下  为什么这次是真的
Wait. Why is that personal?
-闭嘴  蒂娜  -好吧
- Tina, shush. - Okay.
我们终于开成餐馆了
We finally get to run the restaurant.
今日汉堡  "顶级屁股汉堡" 你的脸长得像屁股
我们会成功的
And we're gonna do it right.
我看看
Let's see.
可以把那面墙拆了  做成免下车外带区
We can blow that wall out, put the drive-thru there.
不  我们要200只鸡
No! We need 200 chickens.
从现在开始  我们只卖家禽类的食物
From now on, we only serve poultry!
不  我们只卖甘蓝
No, we only serve kale.
还应该把椅子换成跑步机
And we should replace our chairs with treadmills.
我们会是小镇里最健康的餐馆
We'll be the healthiest restaurant in town.
-顾客会饿着离开  -不不
- People will leave hungry. - No, no.
我们需要的是来了就不走的肥胖顾客
We want fat people who can't leave our restaurant.
-不  跑步机  -鸡肉
- No, treadmills. - Chicken!
跑步机
Treadmills.
在跑步机上供应鸡肉  不能再妥协了
Chicken on a treadmill, last offer.
成交
Okay.
欢迎光临鸡鸡餐馆  你那鸡嘴想吃什么
Welcome to McChickies. What can I put in your beak?
我要芝士汉堡和薯条
Uh... I'll have a cheeseburger and fries?
好的  只需再加两美元
Great, and for only two dollars more,
就能让你的汉堡鸡鸡化
you can have your burger chickenized. Ba-kok!
不了  我想我不需要
No, I don't think I want that.
我给你做个甘蓝砂锅吧
I could offer you a kale-sserole.
或者甘蓝煎饼也行
Or a kale-sadilla.
那啥  我忘记付停车费了
You know what? I forgot to feed the meter.
你不是刚从船上下来吗
Didn't you just get off a boat?
是...停船费  先走了
It's the... boat meter. Got to go!
等等  我还做了个鸡鸡帽呢
Wait. I made a chicken hat.
你没发现吗
Did you not notice it?
好了  各位  听我说
Okay, guys, bring it in. Ugh!
我们为什么会认为开餐馆是个好主意呢
Why did we ever think a restaurant was a good idea?
爸妈多年来的失败我们不是看在眼里吗
We've watched Mom and Dad fail at it for years.
他们让失败变得好容易
They make failing look so easy.
他们怎么做到的
How do they do it?!
如果我们开的是一个
But what if there was a restaurant
不卖食物只提供赌场的餐馆呢
that didn't serve any food and just served up gambling?
赌博不是犯法的吗
I thought gambling was illegal.
没人看见就不算了啊
Not if no one sees you do it.
不  我想还是算的
No, I think it still is.
没人知道就不算了啊
But not if no one knows about it.
我还是认为我们也许
I still think maybe we should...
我们开定了  蒂娜
We're doing it, Tina!
急诊室
-天呐  -抱歉
- Okay. - Sorry.
你觉得这是断了吗
Hey, do you think this is broken?
-拜托  别这样  -看  我能这样
- Please, no. - Look what I can do with it.
我有点头晕了
I'm feeling light-headed.
我们换个地方  走  走
All right, moving seats! Go, go!
没地方可换了
There's nowhere to go.
回咳嗽哥那儿去
Oh, back to Cough Guy.
不  不要又回去
No, not back there! Oh.
欢迎回来
Welcome back.
我忍不了了
I can't take it anymore!
我要出去
I got to get out of here!
-鲍勃・贝尔彻  -到我们了
- Bob Belcher? - That's us!
夫妻二人组进来咯
Party of two, coming through!
看  二位  这是我们自己的地下赌场
Look at it, guys... our very own underground casino.
绞肉机赌场
The Meatgrinder!
这名字是为了向我们的绞肉机致敬吗
Did you name it after our meat grinder?
安迪和奥利会暗中在小镇宣传
Andy and Ollie will discreetly spread the word around town.
秘密赌场  秘密赌场
Secret casino! Secret casino!
嘘  大家别说出去  是秘密的  嘘
Shh! Keep it quiet, though, because it's a secret! Shh!
让齐克当保镖
We'll get Zeke to run the door.
战而必胜  欢迎坐镇
Play to win? Come on in.
你是书呆子  快来扔骰子
You're a nerd? Join the herd.
我还请了四年级的数学达人
And I've hired the fourth grade mathletics geeks
来当发牌员
to be our dealers.
蒂娜  你负责招待客人
Tina, you're in charge of hospitality.
汽水  零食  拍马屁
Sodas, snacks, pats on the backs.
-好的  -吉恩
- Okay. - Gene,
你负责娱乐部分
you're in charge of the entertainment.
我有个很棒的团队
I've got a great group.
超完美的
They'll be perfect...
-"娇俏惹人爱"组合  -啥
- the Cutie Patooties. - The what?
是我组的一个女子组合
It's a girl group I've been putting together.
我在垃圾里找到了这个假发
Hey, I found these wigs in the trash.
我们组一个女子组合如何
I say we start a girl group!
就叫"娇俏惹人爱"  谁要加入
We'll call 'em the Cutie Patooties! Who's in?
有一名成员了
Oh, we got one!
不不不  我没兴趣
Oh, no, no, no. I'm not interested.
我是去上厕所的
I'm just going to the bathroom.
-真倒胃口  -我加入
- Gross. - I'll do it.
很好  但得给你取个艺名
Great! But you're gonna need a stage name.
你真名叫什么
What's your real name?
多蒂・密涅瓦
Dottie Minerva.
好吧  现在你就叫...
Well, now you're, hmm...
-吉什小妞  -我也要加入
- Misty Gish. - I'll join, too.
太好了  那你就叫...
Great. Let's call you...
多蒂・密涅瓦
Dottie Minerva.
-我也加入  -名字用完了
- I want to do it, too. - We're out of names.
那不如就叫你...
So you'll have to be...
三号女孩
Girl Number Three.
我就充当监控器  监视全场动态
And I'll be the eye in the sky, watching over everything.
尤其是赌金
Especially the money.
-但我还是得当你们的保姆  -好好好
- But I'm still babysitting. - Yeah, yeah, yeah.
别让你那空荡荡的小脑瓜费神了
Don't you worry that pretty little empty head.
快去上饮料
Just serve those drinks, huh?
还好吗
Hey, how's it going?
我是艾格曼医生
I'm Dr. Eigerman.
看看那张脸
Look at that face!
多嫩啊
So young!
-我都想喂他喝奶了  -多谢夸奖
- I want to breastfeed that face! - Thanks.
我想我需要缝几针
Ah, ah, I think I just need a few stitches.
缝针  好极了
Stitches. Great.
是医生都能干这个
Those are no problem for a doctor.
是指裆呢
Hey! Finger crotch.
为什们大家都这么叫
Why do people keep calling it that?
因为手指就像两条腿
Ah, because your fingers are like the legs
-腿中间呢就是  -别这样  住手
- and then in the middle, it... - Don't do that. Stop.
好吧  马上给你缝针
All right, let's stitch you right up, here.
好疼啊
Ow! Oh, boy.
-看着我  看着我  -我要晕了
- Look at me, look at me. - I'm gonna faint.
看着我  会没事的
Look at me. You'll be fine.
他是医生
Ah... He's a doctor.
记得那次不  我们去度假
Remember that time, we were on vacation,
你泡在水里  游来游去  是吧
and you were in the water, you're swimming around, right?
专心点  专心点  你很享受
Focus, focus! And you're having fun.
你很享受  有没有
Oh, you're having fun, right?
-我不记得了  -看见没
- I don't remember that. - See?
等等  你在看视频吗
Wait, are you watching a video?
-是的  -关于什么的
- Mm... yes. - About what?
怎样缝针...
How to give stitches...
-怎样缝针吗  -对  我...
- Of how to give stitches? Yeah. My...
短信来了
Oh, text here. Coming in.
谁发的
Who is it?
我老妈
My mom.
妈妈一定很以你为荣
Mommy must be proud of her little doctor.
没错  今晚我们会一起庆祝
Yeah. We're celebrating tonight.
这是我独立行医的第一天
It's my first day without the attending physician supervising me.
等下  第一天
Wait. First day?
第一位病人
First patient!
要我给你拍张照片发给你妈妈吗
Oh, you want me to take a picture for your mommy?
鲍鲍  给我俩照张相
Bobby, you take a picture of us.
琳  我的...  我有点
Well, Lin, my... I kind of...
鲍勃  拿着  快拿着
Bob, take it. Take it.
好吧
All right, fine.
缝针  缝针
Stitches. Stitches.
口令是什么
What's the password?
给你个提示  和"乌贼侦缉"押韵
Here's a hint: Rhymes with "Squid narcs."
-刹车痕迹  -好了  进来吧
- Skid marks. - Okay. Get on in there.
一杯水  一罐非炸死
One water, one fizzazz...
一种在容器底部涂加特殊物质以加快二氧化碳释放速度  提高泡沫持久性的加工饮料
要热毛巾么  有人要热毛巾吗
Hot towel? Hot towel, anyone?
姑娘们  准备好施展你们的娇俏魅力吧
All right, Patooties, get your Cutie faces on.
吉什小妞  你来领唱
Misty, you're singing lead.
是时候一闪你们的明星光彩了
And it's time for this star to shine.
像彩排那样表演就成
Just like we rehearsed.
我们没排练过
We didn't rehearse.
我的天  我们没排练过
Oh, my God, we didn't rehearse.
没排练更好  有新鲜感  快上台吧
All right, even better. It'll be fresher. Go out there.
-快快  快快  快  -我要怎么做
- Go, go, go, go, go. Go. - What do I do?
女孩就是女孩就是女孩
Girls being girls being girls
就是女孩  女子组合
being girls... girl group!
女孩就是女孩就是女孩
Girls being girls being girls
-就是女孩  -不对  不对
- being girls...  - No, no, no, no.
我悄悄唱  你不用啊
I whisper, you don't whisper.
你要大声唱出来
Oh. You-you sing it.
女孩就是女孩就是女孩
Girls being girls being girls being girls...
回来  回来  回来
Come back, come back, come back.
今晚还不到你发挥的时候
Not your night, not your night.
女子组合
Girl group!
歌手们要稍微离开下
Uh, we're gonna take a quick fiver.
技术上遇到些困难
Technical difficulties.
同时  欢迎萨米・夏甲为大家表演
In the meantime, Sammy Hagar, everybody.
快点  快点  下注了各位
Come on, come on, keep those bets coming, people.
赢钱  赢钱  汉堡晚宴
Winner, winner, burger dinner!
露易丝  为什么我们只能穿内裤呢
Louise, why are we in our underwear?
这样你们就不能在数钱的时候中饱私囊了
So you don't steal any of that money you're counting.
我偷了一个西红柿  对不起
I stole a tomato. I'm sorry.
没关系  你也不是故意的
Oh, it's all right. You didn't mean it.
就是饿了吧  朋友
You were just hungry, huh, friend?
-是的  -看见有个西红柿  你就想
- Yeah. - Saw a tomato and you were like,
"藏到内裤里就好了"
"Hey, I know where this goes... in my underwear."
-没错  -老实给我数钱
- Yeah... - Just count the money!
F-9战斗机
F-9.
你炸了我的军舰
You torpedoed my frigate.
你赢了
We've got a winner.
是吗  恭喜啊
All right. Congratulations.
我看你这都是四连胜了
Well, I noticed that's your fourth win in a row.
真够幸运的
You're lucky...
-有点幸运过头了  -谢谢
- a little too lucky. - Uh, thanks.
我打算去兑现了
I was just about to cash out.
别急呀  瞧你满头大汗的
Ah, not so fast, forehead sweat.
我看你朋友在那边
I also noticed your friend over there
一直给你打手势
giving you hand signals.
我想你也该认识下我朋友
Well, I'd like to introduce you to my friend.
齐克
Zeke.
你知道揪咪咪是啥吗
You know what a purple nurple is?
-知道  -朋友  那你要钱
- Yes. You can keep the money, friend.
还是要咪咪
Or you can keep your nurple.
-二选一  -我要咪咪
- But you can't keep both. - Not my nurples!
那就赶紧走  快滚
Now get out of here! Scram!
没什么可看的  大家  蒂娜
Nothing to see here, folks! Tina!
给那边来点喝的  随便点  算我账上
Drinks over here. On the house, whatever they want.
你怎么了  为什么哭了
What do you want? Why are you crying?
我的零花钱输光了
I lost my allowance.
在绞肉机赌场可不许哭
No tears at the Meatgrinder...
只能狂欢
just fun!
啧啧啧
Well, well, well.
本想来借个厕所  看看我发现了什么
I came in to use the bathroom, and what do I find?
一个地下赌场
An underground casino.
还真是在地下啊
That's actually underground.
这地盘是谁的
Who owns this building?
对了  没错
Oh, yes, that's right.
是我的
I do.
谁是这负责人
Who's in charge here?
我们是合资创业
We are a group of entrepreneurs,
不过主要是我的主意
but it was my idea.
那你就摊上大事了  小姑娘
You are in very big trouble, young lady.
因为我是个赌徒
Because I am a gambling man.
一百美元的"拯救山姆"
One hundred dollars on Surgery Sam.
一款玩家充当外科医生取出病人体内异物的游戏
开玩吧
Let's play.
太好了
Yes!
绞肉机要把鲸鱼[赌场大客户]也磨成渣
The Meatgrinder is about to grind up a whale.
等等  我要用金属探测仪检查下你
Hold up, I got to metal-detect you.
可以了  你合格  进去吧
All right, you're good. Go on in.
我是挺喜欢吉什小妞  可她做不来领唱
Look. I love Misty Gish, but she's not ready to sing lead.
你多蒂・密涅瓦才是真正的明星
Dottie Minerva is a star,
是你一闪你明星光环的时候了
and it's time for that star to shine.
女孩就是女孩就是女孩
Girls being girls being girls being girls...
我的天呀  你还不如吉什小妞呢
Oh, my God, oh, my God... you're even worse than Misty Gish.
吉恩  我可以试试
Gene, I could give it a try.
三号女孩  你是候补歌手
Girl Number Three, you're a backup singer.
你连个名字都没有
You don't even have a name.
不过现在只能死马当活马医了  你唱吧
But I guess you'll have to do for now... you're up.
放音乐
Cue the music.
女孩就是女孩就是
Girls being girls being
女孩就是女孩
Girls being girls...
她唱得真好
Wow, she's amazing.
我要让她当明星
I'm gonna make that girl a star.
和我老婆
And my wife.
三号女孩・贝尔彻
Girl Number Three Belcher.
妈的
Oh, damn it.
山姆  你吃汽车是要干嘛
Sam, why would you eat a car?
再来一百美元
Well, another hundred dollars to the house.
还不错  费舍奥德先生
Oh, nice try, Mr. Fischoeder.
下回准能成功
You'll get 'em next time.
-你这么想吗  -对啊  肯定的
- You think? - Yeah, oh, yeah.
-好吧  -总会时来运转的  大叔
- Eh, okay. - Your luck's got to change sometime, buddy.
石头剪刀布
Ooh... Rock, Paper, Scissors.
在古代中国叫做
Or as it was known in ancient China...
猜丁壳
Huo-zhi tou.
你喜欢石头剪刀布吗
Oh, yeah, you like Rock, Paper, Scissors?
想玩吗
You want to play that?
赌一百美元
Hundred dollar bet. Uh...
-来吧  -用美国规则
- Go ahead. - American rules.
数到4同时出...准备
Throw on the four count... ready?
-一  二  -一...
- One, two... - One, mm...
-三  出  -三
- three... shoot! - three...
我赢了  棒极了
I win... fantastic!
没啥大不了的
Ah, it's no big deal.
这点小钱庄家还输得起
The house can lose a few, right?
我们还赢着呢
We're still way up.
那就继续吧
Let's keep this going.
-一二三  -二三
- One, two, three... - Two, three...
-出  -出
- shoot. - shoot.
好了  好了  我亲自来吧
Okay, okay, I'm jumping in here.
换人  换手气  滚开
New dealer, new hand... get out of here.
我做什么了
What'd I do?
-他醒了  -我的天
- Well, that should do it. - Oh, my God.
我好像晕过去了  发生什么了
I think I passed out. What happened?
我只是给你缝了下指裆的伤口
Oh, I just, uh, fixed up the old finger crotch cut.
那为什么我整只手都包起来了
Why is my whole arm bandaged?
我只是想把绷带用完
I thought I'd just kill the roll, you know?
你剃我胳膊的毛了么
Did you shave my arm?
是的
Uh, yeah.
为什么他要剃我胳膊的毛
Why did he shave my arm?
他给你胳膊脱了毛
He shaved your arm.
所以说为什么啊  琳
Why did he shave my arm, Lin?
因为他是医生
Because he's a doctor.
我晕过去的时候发生了什么
What happened when I passed out?
什么也没发生  鲍勃
Bob, nothing.
都在视频里了
It's all on video.
等等  什么视频
Wait, what's on video?
我们录了像  他医治首位病人的情况
We filmed it... it's his first patient.
我要走了
All right, I'm getting out of here.
他妈妈想看啊
His mom wanted to see it.
她很感激
She-she really appreciates it.
我另一支胳膊也被剃毛了
My other arm is shaved!
你干嘛要剃我的毛
Why'd you shave my body?!
他在检查有没有别的伤口
He's looking for other cuts.
-琳  我们走吧  -好吧  再见
- Lin, we're going. - All right... bye.
-一二三  -你要出...
- One, two, three... - You're about to throw...
-出  -石头
- shoot! Aah! - rock!
你怎么知道的
How did you know that?
从我脑袋里滚出去
Get out of my head!
快  再拿点钱过来
Come on, give me some more.
你的钱呢
What do you got?
给我
Give it to me.
没钱了吗
We're out of money?
-那就打欠条吧  -好
- I take IOUs. - Great!
-还玩么  -玩
- Play again? - Yes.
好了  再5分钟就上场了
All right, we're on in five.
你们知道怎么做吧
You know the drill.
三号女孩  你是我们新的一号
Girl Number Three, you're our new number one!
吉恩  我们商量过了
Um, we were talking, Gene, and we've decided that
决定让娇俏惹人爱组合解散了
the Cutie Patooties are breaking up.
解散  可我们才刚起步啊
Breaking up? But this was just the beginning.
我还打算给你们录歌  设计专属香水呢
I was gonna get you an MP3 deal and your own perfume.
惹人爱香水  闻着和女孩的屁一个味儿
Patoot... smells like girl farts.
我要退出
Yeah, well, I'm leaving the business to focus
把精力放在闪光贴纸上了
on my glitter stickers.
我想多花点时间陪我的宠物
And I want to spend more time at home with my pets.
我在学辫法式发辫
And I'm learning how to French braid.
我见你们的时候你们都在学校吃午餐呢
When I met you, you were eating lunch at school.
所以呢
So?
所以  明天学校午餐见
So, see you tomorrow at lunch at school.
我才不需要她们咧
I don't need them.
我自己也可以组女子组合
I can be a girl group all by myself.
反正热情我是不缺的
I certainly have the passion.
剪刀石头布  剪刀石头布
Two, three, shoot. Two, three, shoot!
又赢咯
Another win.
我应该多和小孩儿赌博
I should gamble against children more often.
露易丝  我们好像输了很多钱
Louise, I think we're losing a lot of money.
是吗
Oh, really?
我知道我们输了很多钱
I know we're losing a lot of money!
我感觉得到
I feel it!
但愿我们还能赶回家
Hopefully we can still make it home
应付晚餐高峰
for the dinner rush.
我感觉血不该从这么厚的纱布渗出来吧
Seems like blood shouldn't be able to get through all this.
别意亮  鲍鲍
Stop messing with it, Bobby.
这不  我就知道他是乱缝的
This isn't... I know he didn't do it right.
别管了
Leave it alone.
我就看一小下
I'm just gonna take a quick peek.
鲍鲍  跟你说
Bobby, I said...
我的天呐
Oh, my God!
天呐
-天  看呐  -射进我嘴里了
- Oh, God, look at it! - It went in my mouth!
我吃到你的血了
Oh, I swallowed your blood.
I've swallowed your blood.
-我要晕了  -我要吐了
- Oh, I'm gonna faint. - I'm gonna throw up.
-我要吐了  -啥
- I'm gonna throw up. - What?
我们得回医院了
Oh, we need to go back to the hospital.
-不是吧  -是你们啊
- No. - Hey, it's you guys.
这儿没别的医生吗
Are there any other doctors here?
我不能告诉你
I can't tell you that.
这是医生间的机密
It's doctor-doctor confidentiality.
哪有这种东西
There's no such thing.
我不能透露  但有这种东西
I can't talk about it... but there is.
才没有
No, there's not.
那  那护士好了
I'll-I'll take a nurse.
你是要护士帮你看还是你想带走
You want that for here or to go?
我没懂
I don't get it.
抱歉  以前用都挺好笑的
Sorry, that... that usually kills.
好吧  我去找护士
Okay, I'll go get the nurse.
不过别告诉她我说了那句话
Just don't tell her I said that.
女孩就是女孩就是女孩就是女孩
Girls being girls being girls being girls
女子组合  闭嘴
Girl group, shut your mouth.
谢了  绞肉机的观众们
Thank you, Meatgrinder.
小费就给服务生吧  我跟她爸是朋友
Tip your waitress... I'm friends with her dad.
-一  二  三  -一  二  三
- One, two, three... - One, two, three...
-出  -出
- shoot! - shoot!
-耶  -不
- Yes! - No!
孩子们  我们回来了
Kids, we're home!
快来看看你们老爸的手
Look at your father's arms.
他们把我的毛剃光了
They shaved me.
他看着就像只火鸡
He looks like a turkey.
琳  拜托你去洗洗脸
Lin, wash your face, please.
-否则我又得晕了  -得了吧
- I'm gonna faint again. - Oh, come on.
快看看我
Look at me...
-我的天呐  -孩子们
- Oh, my God. - Kids!
快来看看我血淋淋的脸
Come look at my bloody face.
蒂娜
Tina?
吉恩
Gene?
露易丝  有人吗
Louise? Anybody here?
地下赌场
Underground casino?
外衣褪下  游戏登场
Coat off. Game on.
好了
Well...
我想是时候去兑现了
I think it's time to cash out.
我该去哪儿  我该跟谁...
Where should I, uh, to whom do I, uh...?
-再来最后一把  -不
- Just one more game. - No...
-来嘛  -我结婚之后
- Come on! - If there's one thing I learned
学到的第一件事就是要把握离开的时间
from that week I was married, it's when to walk away.
这是怎么回事
What the hell is going on here?
是啊  怎么回事
Yeah, what is going on here?
露易丝
Louise,
这两个人不知道怎么闯进来了
these two snuck in somehow.
像忍者一样
Like some kind of ninjas.
嗨  老爸老妈  你们回来啦
Hi, Mom and Dad, whoa, you're back.
-鲍勃  -费舍奥德先生
- Bob. - Mr. Fischoeder?
来得正好  我正要
Perfect timing. I was just about to, uh,
-收集战利品呢  -战利品
- collect my winnings. - Your winnings?
这边赌场欠了我一笔钱
Yes, the house owes me some money.
你应该就是赌场主人吧
And I believe you are the house.
我的天
Oh, my God.
赌场欠你多少钱
Uh, how much does "The house" Owe you?
5千美元
$5,000.
啥
What?!
恭喜你  先生
Congratulations, sir.
抱歉  老爸  我的任务就是这个
Sorry, Dad, it's my job.
你也来啦  棉花糖糖
Oh, hey, Marshmallow.
这是怎么回事  发生什么事了
What is this? Wha-What's going on here?
这开了个地下赌场
Well, it's an underground casino.
你们应该在楼上的
You kids are supposed to be upstairs.
楼上的空间不够开赌场
Well, there's no room for a casino upstairs.
你拿着妈咪的咸饼干做什么
What are you doing with Mommy's crackers?
得让客人高兴啊
Got to keep the players happy.
调点小情  送点秋波
Flirt a little, wink a little.
抱歉打断一下  贝尔彻一家
Sorry to interrupt, Belcher family, but, um,
你们貌似还没解决我5千元欠款的事呢
there seems to be a certain unresolved matter of my $5,000.
费舍奥德先生  你不指望我真的还钱吧
Mr. Fischoeder, you can't expect me to pay you.
他们只是孩子在玩扮家家的游戏
I mean, they're just kids playing pretend casino.
你们就不能像正常小孩一样玩游戏吗
Why can't you play like normal kids?
你就不能像正常老爸一样流血吗
Why can't you bleed like a normal dad?
赌了就是赌了  鲍勃
A bet is a bet, Bob.
我曾经买马花了3万块
I once lost $30,000 on a horse.
结果她直接骑着马私奔了
She just ran off with it.
我  我还不起  费舍奥德
Listen, I-I can't afford this, Mr. Fischoeder.
那我就每月多收一千元的房租
Well, I'll just raise your rent by a thousand dollars
五个月就可以还清了
a month for five months.
老爸  能跟你说句话吗
Dad, a word... in private?
-不行  -要不开个家庭会议吧
- No. - Family meeting, huh?
老妈  开家庭会议吧
Mom, family meeting?
-不行  -开家庭会议咯
- No. - Ooh, family meeting.
失陪一下  费舍奥德先生
Excuse us a second, Mr. Fischoeder.
去吧
Certainly.
我们可以赌最后一把
We could play him double or nothing.
啥  不行
What? No.
我们已经陷进去了
We're already in the hole.
我才不要再多输给他5千块呢
I'm not gonna owe him $10,000.
老爸  我赢不了他  但你可以
Dad, I can't beat him, but you can.
用你这只手
With that.
这个  我为什么要用这只手跟他玩
This... why would I play him with this?
我刚缝了针
My hand's stitched.
再说我也不是左撇子
Plus, I'm not even left-handed.
正是这样  你用那只手的话
Exactly... if you use that hand,
他就会以为你不能出剪刀
he'll think you can't throw scissors.
你就偏给他出剪刀
And that's why you're gonna throw scissors.
但我确实不行啊
But I really can't.
我手指分不开呢
My fingers won't separate.
对  在他面前就这么说
Yeah, keep saying that.
我们得让他以为你是这么想的
We need him to think you think that.
不  露易丝  我真的办不到
No, Louise, I can't actually do it.
很好  看来你了解我的意思了
Great, so you know what you have to do.
我的天
Oh, my God.
这才是我的乖女儿
That's my girl.
心理战术的小专家
That's my little mind-gamer.
我的小女神
My little "Amarosa."
可万一费舍奥德先生知道
But what if Mr. Fischoeder knows
我们认为她以为老爸不会出剪刀呢
that we think that he thinks that Dad can't throw scissors?
万一他认为我们知道他是那样想的呢
Or what if he thinks that we know that he thinks that?
万一他认为
Or what if he thinks...?
都有可能  蒂娜  人生就是一场混乱
Any outcome is possible, Tina, life is chaos!
吉恩  你穿着那个干嘛
Gene, why are you wearing that?
我只是个不愿再听别人
I'm just a girl with a dream who got tired
对她说"不"的女孩
of hearing the word no!
喂  贝尔彻家  时间就是金钱哦
Uh, hello, Belchers... time is money,
-是你们还钱的时候了  -我跟他赌
- and I believe it's pay me o'clock. - I'm gonna play him.
鲍鲍  你说真的吗
Bobby, are you sure?
那可是不小的数目哦
That's a lot of money.
我们没得选了  琳
We don't have any other choice, Lin.
他要涨房租  这是唯一的办法
He's gonna raise the rent... I have to.
鲍鲍  你的指裆
Bobby, your finger crotch
看着就像70年代的色情片
looks like a '70s porno.
费舍奥德先生  我们有个提议
Mr. Fischoeder, we have a proposition.
太好了
Wonderful.
你和我
You and me...
石头剪刀布  最后一把
Rock, Paper, Scissors, Double or nothing.
我喜欢
Oh, I like this.
一把全押
One match for all the beans.
如果我输了  你就不欠我了
If I lose, you owe me nothing.
如果我赢了  你就得还我一万块
If I win, you pay me $10,000.
要么翻倍要么啥也没有
Double or nothing,
我穿内裤也一直秉持这个理念
that's also my approach to underpants.
我们开始吧
Shall we dance?
剪刀石头布
Rock, Paper, Scissors.
-一  -剪刀石头布
- One... - Rock, Paper, Scissors.
-二  -剪刀石头布
- two... - Rock, Paper, Scissors.
-三  -剪刀石头布
- three... - Rock, Paper, Scissors.
出
shoot!
你做到了  鲍鲍
Oh, you did it, Bobby!
我看错你了  鲍勃
I misread you, Bob.
没想到你用那只手也能出剪刀
Didn't think could throw scissors with that hand.
我一直认为你挺
I thought you were a little bit of a...
-挺懦弱来着  -就跟你说了嘛老爸
- a wussy. - Told you, Dad.
我让你脱险了
I got you out of this.
不  是你把我拽进来的
No, you got me into this.
然后又把你拉出去了
And out of it.
-进  进  进  -出  出  出
- In, in, in, in, - Out, out, out, out,
- in, in, in. - out, out, out.
-够了  -出
- Stop. - Out.
那么我们两不相欠了
Well, I guess we're even.
或者我们倒回去  再翻个番
Or we run it back... double the double.
-两千块  赌一把  来吧  -行啊
- 20 grand, one throw... let's do this. - I'm game.
你现在手气正好  老爸  别浪费
You've got a hot hand, Dad, use it.
没错  乘胜追击  来个二连冠
Yeah, keep the luck going, Meryl Streak.
不不  已经结束了
No, no, this is over.
不能再赌了
No more gambling.
也就是说我们没事咯
So we're not in trouble anymore?
你们当然有事
Of course you're in trouble.
你能调整下方向吗
Could you point that in another direction?
-抱歉  -算了
- Sorry. - Eh, it's all right.
这血飙得太疯狂了
That's... crazy stream of blood.
好多血哦
That's a lot of blood...
如果你晕过去就说明我们没事了
Pass out if we're not in trouble.
你们没事了
You're not in trouble...
太好了
Yay!
好了  孩子们  帮我把他抬到车上去
All right, kids, help me get him in the car.
我们回医院去
We're going back to the hospital.
太好了
Yay!
音乐
Hit it.
哦  已经有了
Oh, he did.
*鲍勃一流血*
*When Bob sees blood*
*就尖叫着昏了过去*
*And screams and passes out*
*费舍先生于是就来我家骗钱了*
*Then Mr. Fisch checks in and cashes out*
*让小屁孩经营餐馆*
*What more do you want*
*你还能指望什么呢*
*When kids run the restaurant?*
*嗨  水手们*
*Hey, sailor.*
裤子挺漂亮
Ooh, nice pants.
*棉花糖糖玩了个"拯救山姆"的游戏*
*Marshmallow played a game of Surgery Sam*
*于是鲍勃切到了自己的手指*
*And all this 'cause Bob cut his hand*
*让小屁孩经营餐馆*
*What more do you want*
*你还能指望什么呢*
*When kids run the restaurant?*